Farming Life in Another World
Vampires really don't like mornings, do they?
But still, having Lu living here with me
has helped out in all sorts of ways.
We should be all set for lights now.
Wow, that's amazing!
But that's just basic magic.
This has a really mild flavor.
Do you prefer not to use salt
when you cook?
Nope. I just don't have any.
Huh?
Salt.
I've been looking for it for a while,
but I can't find any.
I'm at the point where I'm about to give u-
That's a pretty intense look on your face.
Of course it is.
Right here.
This is mostly salt.
We can dissolve some
then boil it to get salt.
Did you not notice while you were digging?
That's a pretty intense look on your face.
Good morning.
Yeah. Good morning.
What are we doing today?
Let's see...
I was planning to check on
how the fruit trees are growing.
Okay.
I'm going to get washed up,
then I'll head over there.
Look at these.
Did you transplant them to the soil here?
Yup.
They need more time to grow
than the vegetables.
I tried planting oranges
and peaches this time.
I think I might plant chestnuts next time.
Oh yeah?
I can't wait to see how they turn out.
By the way...
The herb tea that Lu makes is pretty good,
but I want to drink green tea.
If I remember correctly,
oolong tea and black tea
are all made from processing
the same leaves...
What is it this time?
Enough!
Please forgive me!
I understand that I was wrong
for attacking you first!
I've seen this situation play out before.
Please rescue me!
Okay.
Are you alright?
Yes, I think so.
Wow, that's amazing!
It's nice to be able to use magic, huh?
Lu?
So this is where you were hiding, Lulucy!
Stop resisting and come in quietly!
Hey, hey, hey!
Jeez... I can't believe you hid
in this forest of all places.
Well, a lot of stuff happened.
That was an awful experience
I just went through.
I know. They did that to me, too.
You too?
Yeah. They're pretty ruthless.
Magic doesn't really affect them much,
plus they dodge spells.
Fighting them is a death sentence...
Yeah...
They seem to have a shared experience.
By the way...
Who is this person?
I'm...
Oh, this person is, um...
My husband.
Your husband?!
You and Lulucy are a couple?!
Huh? Yeah...
I wasn't expecting that.
Um, I'm Hiraku.
Her husband...
That's the first time she's called me that.
Allow me to introduce myself properly.
I'm Tia.
As you can see, I'm an angel.
An angel? So...
That means you serve God, right?
It's nothing that important.
They're simply a race of warriors
that have more muscles than brains.
How rude!
There was a brief time period when
we were an object of worship, you know!
So why is an angel like you
chasing down Lu?
There's a bounty on her because of
all the damage she caused in town
when she went on a rampage.
There's a bounty on your head
because of a rampage?
Well, yeah.
There was a really annoying noble
who kept forcing me to make
medicine and drugs for them.
They were so incessant with their demands
that I felt the need to
teach them a little lesson...
There was nothing little about that lesson!
She spends all her time researching
strange medicines and concoctions,
and then as soon as something bothers her...
she starts blowing everything up!
That's the problem.
Stop making it sound like this is
something I've done multiple times!
That was just an accident!
Regardless, the fact remains that you
besmirched the honor of a noble!
Do you have any idea how high your bounty is?
They seem to get along pretty well.
Well, I do think I went a little too far.
I'm surprised at how willing
you are to admit that.
So anyways, the reason I ended up here
is because I was running from Tia.
After all, she is stronger than I am.
But only a little.
Lulucy, you really have changed.
You never used to be the kind of person
who would admit any weakness.
Yeah, well...
I felt firsthand just how weak
I really was...
I see.
Fighting that many at once
should be against the rules.
Yeah...
Putting that stuff aside...
do you want to live here, too?
Huh? Live here?
Yes, here. Right?
Y-yeah...
I'll show you around the crop fields and stuff.
I'm sure you'll love it here, too!
Let's get going, okay?
Sure...
Look!
These are the crop fields.
We grow lots of vegetables here!
Wow...
And this is our orchard. We have a lot of
different kinds of fruit growing here.
Whoa...
And this...
is Zabuton!
Yeah. That's about what I expected.
Maybe she doesn't like spiders.
Hey!
We're about to harvest some crops.
Come with us.
It's a lot of fun!
Okay...
Did you plant this all yourself, Hiraku?
Yup.
I helped a little, too.
I was just thinking we needed
another set of hands.
You're really saving us here.
Huh? You mean I'm going to
do farm work, too?
Of course.
Come on!
Why does an angel like me have to
get her hands dirty with garden work?
Okay then, let's get started
with the cabbage.
Give it a try just like that.
O-okay...
These are pretty heavy, huh?
Want to give it a taste?
Here.
Well, all I did was tear up some cabbage leaves
I washed and sprinkle salt on them...
It's delicious. Really!
Glad to hear it.
Fresh vegetables really do
taste great, don't they?
Yeah. And the ones you grow yourself
taste even better.
I think you're right.
I think that's enough for today.
Yeah, that's plenty.
I'm exhausted.
It's nice to have so much
but harvesting them all is hard work.
I wish I could do that...
It's delicious!
This vegetable you call a strawberry
is so sweet and tart.
It sure is.
This farming work is a lot more
fulfilling than I expected it to be.
You had fun today, right?
Yes.
Well then, that settles it!
You're going to live here with us, right?
Um...
Right? Come on, please!
My body won't be able to
handle everything if I'm alone.
Excuse me?
What do you mean by that?
Tia, this farming work
really does suit you well.
Was that supposed to be a compliment?
Of course!
Very well. We'll leave it at that.
More importantly...
Hiraku.
Can we make a lot more strawberries?
I really wish we could, but even if
we expanded the crop fields,
we wouldn't be able to keep up
with all the harvesting.
I think we're currently operating at
about maximum capacity now.
Hm...
We really could use
some more help around here.
You can just work hard enough
to make up the difference, Tia.
What about you?
Are you sure you haven't been slacking off?
I don't think she is.
Besides, if we grow too much
then we might not be able to finish
eating everything that we harvest.
Oh, it's the new puppies.
Their horns are already coming in.
Good boy.
Kuro and Yuki's children...
had children of their own.
They've become quite a large family of dogs.
Before long, the puppies are going to
go off and find partners of their own.
Does that mean even more puppies?
Now that you mention it,
that hut isn't going to be big enough.
And so, we decided to build
a dog area next to the orchard.
Orchard
Dog Area
It looks kind of like a horse stable,
but I'd like to think that it turned out well.
For the record, I still haven't
come up with names
for the next generation
after Kuroone and his siblings.
I want to give them names,
Kuro
Yuki
Kuroone  Alice
Kurotwo  Ilice
Uno  Kurothree
Kurofour  Elis
but there are so many of them that it's hard
to come up with names for everyone.
On the other hand, Zabuton's children...
What is it?
...are riding the wind
and starting a new journey.
I guess they're all leaving.
I was planning on turning the orchard
into their new home. Oh well.
It looks like some of them are still
staying behind with us.
Hey.
I'm going to step out for a while, too.
You're going off somewhere
and leaving us too, Tia?
No, I won't be gone for too long.
Now then.
I wonder what she's going off to do.
Well, she's be back before you know it.
You think?
Farming Life...
in Another...
World
A few days later,
Tia came back just like Lu said she would.
And she brought a bunch of girls with her.
You're elves?
We're high elves, but you can
call us elves if you like.
What's the difference?
Please introduce yourselves, everyone.
I'm Lea.
I'm Leef.
I'm Lecott.
I'm Leezay.
I'm Leely.
I'm Leeta.
I'm Lees.
You're all Le.
Ah, you mean our names?
We have similar names
because we're all related.
We came here after Tia suggested
that we all move here.
Please let us all live here with you!
Um...
The truth is, they all share
a very sad backstory.
They all used to live in a village
far to the north.
But most of their people were wiped out
after they got dragged into
the war of the humans.
Their race was scattered, and since then
they've been wandering the land
looking for a place they could
settle down and call home.
We've been travelling through the woods
trying to get by until now.
Without a place to settle down,
we aren't able to repopulate our race.
We ask that you please help us!
Please help us!
You can count on them to be
excellent workers.
I implore you to help them as well.
I think it's a good idea, too.
I've heard the high elves are
a very talented race.
You're all still pretty young, right?
I'm the oldest one,
and I'm just over 400 years old.
I'm the youngest, and I'm about 300.
I can't tell they're 100 years apart.
What do you think?
It's fine, right?
Well, we have a lot of different
roommates living here,
but if you all promise to get along
then I don't have any problem with this.
Thank you very much!
By the way, who are the other roommates?
This is Zabuton.
And these...
are the dogs.
Yeah, that's about how
I expected it to go.
The number of people living here
went up all of a sudden,
so we needed to build
somewhere for them all to live.
Lea said the seven of them
all wanted to live together,
so we decided to build them
one big house.
First, we started with the ditch
and the wooden fence.
Then, we made them their own toilet
and garbage disposal area.
That was an unbreakable giant tree
that's harder than steel.
He cut it like it was nothing.
When it comes to construction,
they know more than I do.
And they're all really handy, too.
I even got to learn a lot about
how to process lumber
and fit the logs together from them.
I just followed their orders.
I focused on digging holes,
and leveling the ground,
and gathering lumber for them.
It took us ten days, and then...
It's finished.
Yeah!
That's amazing.
It's so much nicer than our little hut.
It really is.
Jealousy...
Is he sulking?
It looks like it.
But now I've learned it... their technique!
It might be a good idea to try rebuilding
the little hut we've been sleeping in.
The house is shaped like a long rectangle
that stretches from east to west.
Just past the entrance way,
there's the large living room
that doubles as a dining room.
It's a place to work on things together,
or so they can all eat together.
Sitting on both the left and right sides of
the living room are storage rooms.
Living Room
Storage
The living room is an open design
that covers the first and second floors.
The lighting is done with magic.
And the second floor rooms sit
on top of the storage rooms.
The second floor is where
their individual rooms are.
I hope that this can become a home
where they feel safe and at peace.
It looks like they've all
gotten used to life here.
Yeah.
The vegetable harvesting is going great.
Yup.
They're eating raw garlic they just picked.
That's pretty wild.
Huh?
You use fire and you eat meat, too?
Yeah, of course.
When I think of elves...
I think of a race that lives in the woods
and is one with nature,
and hates fire and stuff.
Where'd you get that silly idea?
Am I wrong?
How is anyone supposed to live
without using fire?
Like I said, you're one with nature...
Can you be more specific?
Huh? Well...
You wake up with the sunrise,
and go to sleep when it sets.
You eat fruit from the trees.
And you love the forest trees.
And you refuse to wear
anything made of metal...
Excuse me, Hiraku.
Hm?
Please stop underestimating
how harsh nature can be.
If you tried living like that in the forest,
you'd die right away.
I-I see...
Good.
They really are hardcore survivalists.
By the way, as thanks for
letting us all live here,
we were planning on doing some mining
and blacksmithing work for you.
Huh? You guys can do that?
We can.
I'd like to start by building
a furnace that can melt iron.
I always imagined that dwarves handled
all blacksmithing related work.
I guess that's different in this world.
Following Lea's instructions, they quickly
put together a smithing work station.
They put charcoal and
iron sand taken from the river
Charcoal
Iron Sand
into the earthen furnace and heat it up.
Then they hammer the melted iron
to process it.
This is great!
Our civilization is advancing!
Thank you very much.
You can really do everything, can't you?
Well, that tends to happen
when you spend the better part of
200 years wandering without a home.
I see.
The only things we couldn't do...
was settle down for good and reproduce!
Well, we already took care of one of those!
I thought it would be for the best
if I didn't say anything about
the second thing she mentioned.
I'm really happy you guys
all came to live here.
Me too.
I'm happy to hear that you feel that way.
Let's stop here for today.
Excuse me.
I believe I saw a wheat field out over there.
Yeah, we have one,
but we already processed all the wheat
we harvested into flour so we could store it.
If it's alright with you,
I'd like to bake some bread.
Bread? Please go ahead!
What's that?
If you use this stuff, it makes the bread
rise up when it bakes.
That freshly baked bread tasted amazing.
This is delicious!
It really is.
We're all very happy to hear that you like it.
That jar must have had a natural yeast
to make the bread rise inside of it.
Now that we can bake bread,
I'd like to expand the wheat fields...
I know it's a little late to be asking this,
but does this land we're on
belong to anyone?
You mean like this forest?
Yes.
I don't think anyone owns this
particular plot of land or anything,
but I guess technically it's under
the control of the demon lord.
The demon lord?!
What the heck? That's scary.
Is there a problem?
Um... do you think the demon lord
is going to have a problem
with me building all these
crop fields and stuff here?
Is that what you're worried about?
Did you receive any kind of support
when you started building all this?
No. Not at all.
Then there's nothing to worry about.
If you built this on your own,
then the land belongs to you.
I guess that's how it works.
Yeah, that's how it works!
Orchard
Dog Area
Elf House
Hiraku is really full of surprises.
He surprised me a lot at first, too.
Not only did he tame all those inferno wolves,
but he tamed a demon spider, too.
He's definitely special.
And these crops...
Is the soil here really good enough
to grow things like this?
Who knows? I never asked him.
I'm sure he has a very green thumb.
That said, it's surprising how lacking he is
in knowledge about the world around him.
Ah! I know what you mean.
He was saying that he thought elves were
a race that didn't use fire or eat meat.
Are you serious?
He didn't seem to know
what angels are, either.
That goes a few steps beyond
just lacking some knowledge.
Yeah, you're right.
Oh yeah, I haven't progressed on
building the waterway in a while now.
Maybe I'll ask Lea and the elves
to help me out.
There's lots of work to do tomorrow.
Next time
Episode 4
Waterways Make Life Feel Complete
Next time